[
    {
        "id": 1,
        "front": "apple",
        "back": "яблоко",
        "setName":"English"
    },
    {
        "id": 2,
        "front": "red",
        "back": "красный",
        "setName":"English"
    },
    {
        "id": 3,
        "front": "blue",
        "back": "голубой",
        "setName":"English"
    },
    {
        "id": 4,
        "front": "car",
        "back": "машина",
        "setName":"English"
    },
    {
        "id": 5,
        "front": "reflection",
        "back": "рефлексия",
        "setName":"English"
    },
    {
        "id": 6,
        "front": "margin",
        "back": "внешний отступ",
        "setName":"css"
    },
    {
        "id": 7,
        "front": "padding",
        "back": "внутренний отступ",
        "setName":"css"
    },
    {
        "id": 8,
        "front": "display",
        "back": "дисплей / экран",
        "setName":"css"
    },
    {
        "id": 9,
        "front": "style",
        "back": "стиль",
        "setName":"css"
    },
    {
        "id": 10,
        "front": "width",
        "back": "ширина",
        "setName":"css"
    },
    {
        "id": 11,
        "front": "a",
        "back": "ссылка",
        "setName":"html"
    },
    {
        "id": 12,
        "front": "button",
        "back": "кнопка",
        "setName":"html"
    },
    {
        "id": 13,
        "front": "h1",
        "back": "заголовок 1-го уровня",
        "setName":"html"
    },
    {
        "id": 14,
        "front": "p",
        "back": "параграф",
        "setName":"html"
    },
    {
        "id": 15,
        "front": "h2",
        "back": "заголовок 2-го уровня",
        "setName":"html"
    }
]